<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="base">
        <!-- What is a launcher -->
        <!-- What is an icon pack -->
        <!-- How do i use an icon pack? -->
        <!-- How do i apply an icon pack? -->
        <!-- How do i see all icons included? -->
        <!-- I can\'t see a complete icon name -->
        <!-- How can i replace icons with an alternate icon? -->
        <!-- How do i request an icon? -->
        <!-- How can i restore remaining Premium Requests after reinstalling the app? -->
        <!-- After restarting my phone, the icon pack is not applied, it restore to defaults? -->
        <!-- Why do the icons looks jaggy or pixelated on my phone? -->
        <!-- I can see the icon included in all icons,
            but why isn\'t the actual icon on app drawer changed? -->
        <!-- What is the \"report bugs\" option? -->
        <!-- My launcher is listed in the google play description, but why isn\'t it included in apply section? -->
        <!-- Wallpaper can\'t be applied, just showing black screen? -->
        <!-- Muzei: How to load downloaded wallpapers only? -->
        <!-- Muzei: I don\'t want to keep downloading wallpapers each time the wallpaper changes? -->
        <!-- Muzei: I only want to use specific wallpapers? -->
        <!-- Why are Read &amp; Write External Storage permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Internet permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Access Network State permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Access Wifi State permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Set Wallpaper permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Wake Lock Permission needed? -->
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>லான்ச்சர் என்றால் என்ன?</item>
        <item>ஐகான் பேக் என்றால் என்ன?</item>
        <item>ஐகான் பேக்கை எவ்வாறு பயன்படுத்துவது?</item>
        <item>ஐகான் பேக்கை எவ்வாறு பயன்படுத்துவது?</item>
        <item>அனைத்து ஐகான்களும் சேர்க்கப்பட்டிருப்பதை நான் எவ்வாறு பார்ப்பது?</item>
        <item>முழுமையான ஐகான் பெயரை என்னால் பார்க்க முடியவில்லை</item>
        <item>மாற்ற ஐகானுடன் ஐகான்களை எவ்வாறு மாற்றுவது?</item>
        <item>ஐகானை நான் எவ்வாறு கோருவது?</item>
        <item>How can i restore remaining Premium Requests after reinstalling the app?</item>
        <item>எனது தொலைபேசியை மறுதொடக்கம் செய்த பிறகு, ஐகான் பேக் பயன்படுத்தப்படவில்லை, அது இயல்புநிலைக்கு மீட்டமைக்கப்படுமா?</item>
        <item>எனது தொலைபேசியில் ஐகான்கள் ஏன் பிக்சலேட்டாக காணப்படுகின்றன?</item>
        <item>I can see the icon included in all icons,
            but why isn\'t the actual icon on app drawer changed?</item>
        <item>What is the \"report bugs\" option?</item>
        <item>எனது லான்ச்சர் கூகிள் பிலே விளக்கத்தில் பட்டியலிடப்பட்டுள்ளது, ஆனால் அது ஏன் விண்ணப்பப் பிரிவில் சேர்க்கப்படவில்லை?</item>
        <item>Wallpaper can\'t be applied, just showing black screen?</item>
        <item>Muzei: How to load downloaded wallpapers only?</item>
        <item>Muzei: I don\'t want to keep downloading wallpapers each time the wallpaper changes?</item>
        <item>Muzei: I only want to use specific wallpapers?</item>
        <item>Why are Read &amp; Write External Storage permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why is Internet permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why is Access Network State permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why is Access Wifi State permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why is Set Wallpaper permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why is Wake Lock Permission needed?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>லான்ச்சர் ஆண்ட்ராய்டு பயனர் இடைமுகத்தின் ஒரு பகுதியாகும், இது முகப்புத் திரையைத் தனிப்பயனாக்க, மொபைல் பயன்பாடுகளைத் தொடங்க, தொலைபேசி அழைப்புகளைச் செய்ய மற்றும் ஆண்ட்ராய்டு சாதனங்களில் பிற பணிகளைச் செய்ய பயனர்களை அனுமதிக்கிறது.</item>
        <item>A set of graphics that will change the look of your app drawer icons</item>
        <item>You will need a launcher that supports custom icon packs.
            Supported launchers are listed in the Play store description.
            If you are confused which launchers should be used, just go to the \"Apply\" section, then install from there.</item>
        <item>You can open the navigation drawer then open \"Apply\". Choose your launcher from the list.
            If your launcher is not listed there but this icon pack is compatible with it
            (see on Google Play Store description for supported launchers),
            you can apply the icon pack manually from your launcher settings.</item>
        <item>You can open the navigation drawer then open \"Icons\"</item>
        <item>Just tap the icon. A preview dialog will appear with a bigger image and complete icon name.</item>
        <item>It depends on which launcher you used. Not every launcher supports icon editing.
       	    Mostly you can edit an icon by tapping &amp; holding the icon or double tapping it.</item>
        <item>You can open navigation drawer then open \"Icon Request\".</item>
        <item>You can open navigation drawer then open \"Settings\", choose \"Restore Purchases\".
            If you had remaining Premium Requests before reinstalling, they will be restored.</item>
        <item>It happened because this icon pack was moved to SD Card, you should install it in internal memory.</item>
        <item>The problem might come from the launcher that you used when handling big icon resolution.
       	    You can fix it by increasing the icon size to 115 - 120%.
       	    Alternatively you might change your launcher.</item>
        <item>Open settings, scroll down, then choose \"Report Bugs\".</item>
        <item>\"Report Bugs\" is used to report bugs related to the icon pack, not the dashboard.</item>
        <item>Not every launcher supports direct apply, and some of them can\'t be accessed directly from the dashboard.
      	    You can apply this icon pack manually from the individual launcher settings.</item>
        <item>When you \"Set Wallpaper\" directly from the app, it will be downloaded to the cache,
      	    then the dashboard app will try to apply it. Applying will take some time and also need a huge amount of RAM for a short timespan.
      	    \"Black Screen\" errors may appear because your phone doesn\'t have enough free RAM to process the wallpaper.
      	    Restarting your phone will fix this problem. After restarting, your phone will have more RAM available.
            Alternatively, you can open the downloaded wallpaper from your Gallery and set it as wallpaper from there.</item>
        <item>Open muzei, choose this icon pack, settings. You will see an option to load downloaded wallpapers only.
            You will need to download wallpapers from the dashboard first.</item>
        <item>If a wallpaper is already downloaded, it will be loaded from your phone memory automatically.
            Muzei won\'t keep downloading it when the wallpaper changes. You will need to download wallpapers from the dashboard first.</item>
        <item>Open Dashboard, download wallpapers that you want to use in Muzei.
            Open Muzei settings, then choose Load Downloaded Wallpapers Only.</item>
        <item>It is used to write &amp; read cache, and collect the icon request data.</item>
        <item>It is used to load Cloud Based Wallpapers &amp; download them.</item>
        <item>It is used to check if your phone has an internet connection or not.</item>
        <item>It is used to check if your phone has an internet connection to a wifi or not, to load cloud wallpapers from Muzei.</item>
        <item>It is used to apply wallpapers directly from the dashboard app.</item>
        <item>It is used by Muzei Live Wallpaper</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
