<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="base">
        <!-- What is a launcher -->
        <!-- What is an icon pack -->
        <!-- How do i use an icon pack? -->
        <!-- How do i apply an icon pack? -->
        <!-- How do i see all icons included? -->
        <!-- I can\'t see a complete icon name -->
        <!-- How can i replace icons with an alternate icon? -->
        <!-- How do i request an icon? -->
        <!-- How can i restore remaining Premium Requests after reinstalling the app? -->
        <!-- After restarting my phone, the icon pack is not applied, it restore to defaults? -->
        <!-- Why do the icons looks jaggy or pixelated on my phone? -->
        <!-- I can see the icon included in all icons,
            but why isn\'t the actual icon on app drawer changed? -->
        <!-- What is the \"report bugs\" option? -->
        <!-- My launcher is listed in the google play description, but why isn\'t it included in apply section? -->
        <!-- Wallpaper can\'t be applied, just showing black screen? -->
        <!-- Muzei: How to load downloaded wallpapers only? -->
        <!-- Muzei: I don\'t want to keep downloading wallpapers each time the wallpaper changes? -->
        <!-- Muzei: I only want to use specific wallpapers? -->
        <!-- Why are Read &amp; Write External Storage permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Internet permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Access Network State permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Access Wifi State permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Set Wallpaper permission needed? -->
        <!-- Why is Wake Lock Permission needed? -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>What is a launcher?</item>
        <item>What is an icon pack?</item>
        <item>How do I use an icon pack?</item>
        <item>How do I apply an icon pack?</item>
        <item>How do I see all icons included?</item>
        <item>Why can\'t I see the complete icon name?</item>
        <item>How can I replace icons with an alternate icon?</item>
        <item>After restarting my phone, why is the icon pack not applied?</item>
        <item>Why do the icons looks jaggy or pixelated on my phone?</item>
        <item>I can see the icon included in the dashboard,
            but why isn\'t it changed on the app drawer?</item>
        <item>What is the \"Report Bugs\" option?</item>
        <item>My launcher is listed in the Google Play description, but why isn\'t it included in the \"Apply\" section?</item>
        <item>Why is my wallpaper a black screen when I apply it from the app?</item>
        <item>Why is Read and Write External Storage permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why is Internet permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why is Set Wallpaper permission needed?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>The launcher is the part of the Android user interface that lets users customize their home screen,
            launch applications, make phone calls, and perform other tasks on Android devices.</item>
        <item>An icon pack is a set of graphics that will change the look of your app drawer icons.</item>
        <item>You will need a launcher that supports custom icon packs.
            Supported launchers are listed in Delta\'s Play Store description.
            If you are confused on which launchers should be used, just go to the \"Apply\" section, and install a launcher from there.</item>
        <item>You can open the navigation drawer, click on \"Apply\", and choose your launcher from the list.
            If your launcher is not listed but Delta is compatible with it
            (see Play Store description for supported launchers),
            you can apply Delta manually from your launcher settings.</item>
        <item>You can open the navigation drawer then open \"Icons\".</item>
        <item>Just tap the icon. A preview dialog will appear with a bigger image and the complete icon name.</item>
        <item>It depends on which launcher you used. Not every launcher supports icon editing.
       	    Mostly, you can edit an icon by tapping and holding the icon, or double tapping it.</item>
<!--        <item>You can open navigation drawer then open \"Icon Request\".</item>-->
<!--        <item>You can open navigation drawer then open \"Settings\", choose \"Restore Purchases\".-->
<!--            If you had remaining Premium Requests before reinstalling, they will be restored.</item>-->
        <item>This occurred because Delta was moved to SD Card storage. You should install it into internal memory.</item>
        <item>The problem might come from the way your launcher handles large icon resolutions.
       	    You can fix it by increasing the icon size to 115-120%.
       	    Alternatively, you can change your launcher.</item>
        <item>Open settings, scroll down, and choose \"Report Bugs\".</item>
        <item>\"Report Bugs\" is used to report bugs related to the icon pack, not the dashboard.</item>
        <item>Not every launcher supports direct application, and some of them can\'t be accessed directly from the dashboard.
      	    You can apply this icon pack manually from your launcher\'s settings.</item>
        <item>When you use \"Set Wallpaper\" directly from the app, it will be downloaded to the application\'s cache,
      	    then the dashboard app will try to apply it. Applying will take some time, and needs a huge amount of RAM for a short time.
      	    Black screen errors may appear because your phone doesn\'t have enough free RAM to process the wallpaper.
      	    Restarting your phone will fix this problem. After restarting, your phone will have more RAM available.
            Alternatively, you can open the downloaded wallpaper from your gallery and set it as your wallpaper from there.</item>
        <item>Read and Write External Storage permission is needed to read and write cache, and collect icon request data.</item>
        <item>Internet permission is needed to download Cloud-Based Wallpapers.</item>
        <item>Set Wallpaper permission is needed to apply wallpapers directly from the dashboard app.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
